<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Portfolio</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Portfolio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2016 22:55:05 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Python Lists vs. Dictionaries</title>
      <link>/blog/python-lists-vs-dictionaries/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/python-lists-vs-dictionaries/</guid>
      <description>The Difference Between a List and Dictionary in Python When learning to code with Python, there are several ways to work with sets of data. Lists and dictionaries are both common methods of storing information, but they have several key differences.
Lists: A list is simply a set of values, organized and stored in a certain order. You can create a list and assign it a name like this:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2016 22:55:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description>Projects Here are some projects I have recently completed:
  Exploratory Data Analysis with Tidyverse Tools (2020): Running Man, Weather Man
  Modeling, Testing, and Classification (2020): Food, People, and Other Counts for Texas Counties
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project #1 - Running Man, Weather Man</title>
      <link>/project1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project1/</guid>
      <description>Running Man, Weather Man Austin, Texas is city that boasts great people and great weather. This project explores the running habits of a local Austinite, Steve, who runs all around town and even partakes in ultra-marathons across the country. Since 2013, Steve has recorded data for many, if not most, of his runs in the fitness app, Strava. With Strava, users can record and upload data about a range of activities including running, biking, hiking, or even watersports.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project #2</title>
      <link>/project2final/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project2final/</guid>
      <description>Food, People, and Other Counts for Texas Counties The USDA broadly defines the term “food desert” as a “neighborhood that lacks healthy food sources.” A given geographic region may be classified as a food desert based on an analysis of various demographic and accessibility factors. The County Health Rankings &amp;amp; Roadmaps survey of Health Data for 2016 provides each county in Texas with a Food Environment Index score, which incorporates measures of grocery store proximity, income level, and food source reliability for each county.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>